Did you remember to lock your door?
You're Next is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Adam Wingard.
When the Davison family comes under attack during their wedding anniversary getaway, the gang of mysterious
killers soon learns that one of their victims harbors a secret talent for fighting back.
Erin, played by Sharni Vinson.
Felix Davison, played by Nicholas Tucci.
Zee, played by Wendy Glenn.
Crispian, played by AJ Bowen.
Drake Davison, played by Joe Swanberg.
Kelly Davison, played by Margaret Laney.
You're Next is a 2011 American slasher film directed and edited by Adam Wingard, written by
Simon Barrett and starring Sharni Vinson, Nicholas Tucci, Wendy Glenn, A.
Bowen, Joe Swanberg, Barbara Crampton, and Rob Moran.
The plot concerns an estranged family under attack by a group
of masked assailants during a family reunion.
Produced on a low budget, You're Next had its world premiere in the Midnight Madness section of the 2011 Toronto
International Film Festival and was released theatrically on August 23, 2013, in the United States.
The film grossed over $26 million from a $1 million production
budget and has since gained a cult following.
The film explores themes of greed, missouri, family
dinner, brother against brother, massacre.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.